function QuestionGenerator(count = 5) {
    const questions = [
        {
            question: "This Bird can run faster than horses, and the males can roar like lions.",
            options: ["Turkey", "Ostrich", "Duck", "Pelican"],
            answer: "Ostrich"
        },

        {
            question: "The female lion does -- percent of the hunting.",
            options: ["60", "75", "90", "85"],
            answer: "90"
        },

        {
            question: "This Animal has no gall bladders.",
            options: ["Cow", "Sheep", "Aardvark", "Deer"],
            answer: "Deer"
        },

        {
            question: "The female -- undergo menopause like the human female",
            options: ["Elephant", "Goriila", "Hippo", "Alligator"],
            answer: "Elephant"
        },

        {
            question: "Male Rabbits are called ...?",
            options: ["Does", "Bucks", "Dows", "Alpha"],
            answer: "Bucks"
        },

        {
            question: "A group of Owls is called a ...?",
            options: ["Parliament", "Legislative", "Senate", "Judiciary"],
            answer: "Parliament"
        },

        {
            question: "The very first bomb that the Allies dropped on Berlin in World War Two hit a ...?",
            options: ["Dog", "Horse", "Cow", "Elephant"],
            answer: "Elephant"
        },

        {
            question: "The -- is the world’s deadliest caterpillar",
            options: ["Lonomia obliqua", "Pyrrharctia isabella", "Spilosoma virginica", "Estigmene acrea"],
            answer: "Lonomia obliqua"
        },

        {
            question: "A ‘haw’ is the third eyelid of a --, which can only be seen when the -- isn’t well.",
            options: ["Dog", "Cat", "Parrot", "Monkey"],
            answer: "Cat"
        },

        {
            question: "Hummingbirds beat their wings how many times per second?",
            options: ["10-20", "100-120", "30-50", "60-80"],
            answer: "60-80"
        },

        {
            question: "A group of butterflies is known as a?",
            options: ["Crown", "Flutter", "Wave", "Crew"],
            answer: "Flutter"
        },

        {
            question: "The African Penguin is also commonly referred to as The JACKASS PENGUIN because ...",
            options: ["It makes Donkey-like braying noises", "It works like a Jackass", "It looks like an Ass", "It has 4 legs"],
            answer: "It makes Donkey-like braying noises"
        }

    ]

    return(
        questions.sort(function(){return (Math.random() - Math.random()) }).slice(0, count)
    ) 
} 

export default QuestionGenerator